Contact

+55 54 981002363

cinthia_becher@hotmail.com

Rio Grande do Sul, Brazil

Skills

Developer Skills

HTML

• • • • • • • •

CSS • • • • • • • • • •

JS • • • • • • • • •

React

Design Skills

Prototyping | Figma

UX/UI

• • • • • • • • •

•••••

••••••

Ideation Process

Soft Skills

Well-organized

• • • • • • • • •

Adaptative

••••••

Problem Solver

Creative

Cinthia Becher

Front-end Developer | Digital Products

About

Since I was a child, I've loved the art of creation. This led me to study Computer Science and get involved with Product Design years later.

As a Product Designer, I thoroughly enjoy the idea of solving real problems with a great user experience. However, as a Front-end developer, I love to bring to life what were just ideas.

Education

Computer Science

Unisinos | 2020 - present

Dell Product Design Program

Unisinos & Dell Technologies | 2021

HTML & CSS Course

Alura | 2022

JavaScript Course

Alura | 2022

Career

Research Study Assistant | Unisinos Volunteer | Part-time | Jul 2020 - Nov 2020

Research into the use of multi-agent reinforcement learning.

Website Developer | Orgânica Digital Internship | Sep 2020 - Apr 2021

Design and build user experiences through WordPress sites using HTML and CSS. I built and helped maintain an online presence for companies and optimized their visibility with SEO tools.

Product Desiner Dell Technologies Internship | Apr 2021 - present

Being involved in the ideation process to design good user experiences in digital products. Working with Figma, prototyping and wireframing screens and components